Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The world decays, in gloom I stray♪
♪Right and wrong, in frost engraved♪
♪On dreams of love, blades clash and sway♪
♪Alone I ride, blood still unswayed♪
♪Through heaven's mirth and earth's despair♪
♪Toasting the moon, I drink the chill air♪
♪Though hearts like battlefields may be♪
♪Let fate write its uncertainty♪
♪From this life to the great unknown♪
♪Who'll stand with me, on thrones unknown?♪
♪I'll wander through this life to guard you♪
♪Through mortal realms, serene I roam♪
♪With you, the world becomes my home♪
♪Unbroken, bold, as I have sworn♪
♪I'll roam this life, and feel no torn♪
♪Our souls embraced, no regret born♪
♪By twilight's lamp, though night be worn♪
♪Through deepest dark, I'll find the morn♪
=Fight For Love=
=Episode 34=
The Queen Mother is here.
Leave this to the servants.
When you were born,
your paranoid uncle
didn't want you here.
So I had to leave you in Great Sui.
I know you've harbored resentment
all these years.
But Yue,
you should understand.
I didn't have a choice, then.
But what's gone is gone.
It's your coronation today.
The throne of North Qi
is finally in our hands.
Our years of planning
finally paid off.
Without your mediation, this day
wouldn't have come so soon.
Thank you, Mother.
When I was subject to Su Can,
I only endured
by clinging to the thought
that this day would come.
Today,
why do you keep talking about the past?
Yesterday, I got a message.
Great Sui agreed to discuss peace.
I've had someone
draft a letter to Emperor Chunde,
asking him to send a delegation
for peace talks.
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
You haven't ascended the throne.
So, I have the duty
to handle these things for now.
What?
Yue,
are you dissatisfied
with my decision?
It is settled.
Yue,
during the peace talks,
you should exchange that woman
for tangible benefits from Great Sui.
Never.
She isn't the Eldest Princess here.
She is my woman, and that is all.
You can make almost any decision.
But regarding Changming,
please let me have my way.
Your Majesty,
it is time.
Since you want her,
I'll let you have your way.
You have to remember.
Li Changming can stay.
But if you lose people's support
or disobey me
because of this woman,
I wouldn't mind
killing one more person.
Mother,
I should go see the officials.
(Qi)
In Year 6 of Yuanle,
Zhao Yue became the King of North Qi.
Queen Mother Yunyang jointly governed.
By the grace of heaven,
I now ascend the throne.
This year will be Year 1 of Qingming.
I'll grant a general amnesty
to celebrate this.
Lords of our sixteen cities
will maintain peace within your cities
and prevent disorder.
I will handle state affairs carefully
to protect our land.
I make a promise to all my subjects.
One day,
I will conquer states
including Great Sui,
South Yue, and West Jing
to unite the whole world.
I've been too busy with the coronation
to give you much attention.
Ping told me
you ate very little
what the King offered.
Does it not taste good?
King?
This word
sounds really fresh
when it comes from your mouth.
Why don't you repeat it,
so I can get used to that?
What?
Do you not think
I can be a good king?
I heard
during the coronation,
Queen Mother Yunyang
was sitting right next to your throne.
Whether you can be
a good king of North Qi...
Is it really up to you?
So what?
I'm the only son
of my mother.
Now, I'm sitting on the throne.
It's what she has been pursuing.
She handles state affairs
just to help me.
You wouldn't
have gotten the throne
without her schemes.
So, she can take back what she gave you.
You're mother and son,
but so what?
A royal family has no affection.
So do the two of you.
I'm on the throne, anyway.
I want everyone to know
that I'm destined to be
the King of North Qi,
and no one can change that.
As for you, Changming...
All you need to do is stay by my side.
When the court stabilizes,
I will make you
my queen.
You will share with me
the most honorable glory.
Hope so.
(Duke of Hu's Mansion)
Governess,
don't bring me any food. I'm not hungry.
What are you doing here?
And the governess?
Father sent her
to watch over me.
Hurry.
Don't worry, Tuantuan.
We hit her gently.
She's fine.
Tuantuan, come with me.
A surprise for you.
Shilan, stop dawdling.
Take off your robe.
I'll take Tuantuan out alone.
I took you here, so you could
pretend to be Tuantuan.
No wonder you said you couldn't
have done this without me.
Min,
get us one outfit of hers.
Turn around.
Come on, move.
Why didn't you tell me before we came?
You...
If I had told you,
you wouldn't have come.
Come on, Wenchang.
Hand.
I'll do it myself.
Oh, My Lady.
My Lady.
My Lady?
My Lady,
you have 80 pages to copy
as your punishment.
(Chu Mansion)
Come on.
Try harder.
Be patient.
Take your time.
It's alright.
Even if you remain like this,
Mother can still carry you
and always take care of you.
When you were a little boy,
I always held you, didn't I?
Now, even Chu Shan can hardly carry me.
Not to mention you.
Don't underestimate me.
Tomorrow, I'll ask Yu
to teach me martial arts.
You're back.
Slow down. Don't choke.
Mother. Linyang.
It's so hard
to rent a shop out there.
I've looked almost everywhere.
They're either too expensive
or too remote.
Why is it so hard
to start a business?
We aren't short of money now.
You can just choose a shop you like.
The herbal medicine business
requires a lot of capital.
And you will get married someday.
We do need money
in many cases.
Mother,
I know
you think for Miss Song.
But if she
truly loves Linyang...
Jin.
You must be hungry now.
I'll go make you something to eat.
Jin.
Stop pressing.
It doesn't work.
Don't try to lie to me, Linyang.
You want so badly to stand up.
Miss Song must be one of the reasons.
You've been telling me
to make sure
what I really want.
Linyang, you aren't leading by example.
I certainly know
what I really want.
But look at me now.
It's a nice day today.
Let me take you out for a walk.
Where will he come from?
Wenchang.
Why did you bring me here?
Is there a surprise?
Tuantuan.
- How are you?
I...
I'm fine.
Why are you here?
I guess some of our friends
wanted us to meet each other.
That's good.
Linyang.
I thought it would get better
as time passed.
But since we see each other here,
I won't escape anymore
or deceive myself.
So,
please don't avoid me, will you?
I'm sorry.
I never made things clear to you,
so you were bothered.
Since I was little, my father taught me
to take responsibilities.
As a son,
I failed to save my father
when he died in a battle,
which broke my mother's heart.
As an elder brother,
I failed to balance
the relationship between my sisters,
so they were estranged for a long time.
I always strove for perfection
while nothing ended up perfect.
Now,
if I accept you rashly
with such a body,
how could I get your parents' approval?
Even if they approve,
how would I not feel sorry?
But Tuantuan,
I want to make this bet with you.
One day,
I will stand up
and go get you back.
Will you wait for me?
♪If not for dreams by windswept flight♪
♪How would my hand find yours tonight?♪
♪This moonlit glow, in dusk's soft veil♪
I've been waiting for this promise.
♪Hears heartbeats
tell their secret tale♪
♪Dawns greet the spring
we longed to see♪
♪Through meadows
where wild larks soar free♪
♪Let countless sails
cross this worldly tide♪
♪When lonely shadows turn to two♪
♪Through countless turns
and all we've borne♪
♪No regret ever could be sworn♪
♪Dawns greet the spring
we longed to see♪
♪Beneath heaven's vault, in harmony♪
♪Let tears now fall
for yesterday's strife♪
♪We've reached
this blossom-covered hill♪
♪I'll follow you through every dream♪
Let me tell you.
My mother
doesn't accept Tuantuan
for her own good.
Don't hold any prejudice against her.
I won't.
On the surface, my mother
doesn't worry about Linyang's legs.
But in secret, she has cried many times.
Linyang and I
pretend we didn't know,
so she wouldn't feel worse.
My family...
Jin,
I just appear to be careless.
But I totally understand
all these things.
Really?
So, why did you get Tuantuan out?
What if your father punishes you?
That's why I'm taking you here
to buy some cushions.
I'll put them on me
before he canes me.
Is your father so harsh?
Don't worry. He won't be harsh to you.
I don't care if he doesn't like me.
Think about who I am.
Listen,
within three days,
I will make him acknowledge me.
I'll choose an auspicious day
for betrothal gifts.
I swear I'll marry you
with a grand wedding.
We're still in public.
Don't say that.
Jin.
I, Song Wenchang,
will marry Chu Jin!
Many officials
accused you of having fun
at Fragrance House
and lacking personal virtue.
(Xuanzheng Hall)
Some even
advised me to strip you
of your noble title.
What do you think?
Your Majesty will decide.
I'll just obey.
Wen Yun,
do you really not want
a better title?
Your Majesty,
my lifelong wish
is to protect our country,
have a proper house,
eat regular meals,
and always live with the one I love.
That's all I want.
Don't forget.
You're first my subject
before you're Wei Yun.
Your Majesty,
in the court,
I can be the general who fights enemies
and recovers lost land.
I'll protect our nation
and its emperor at all costs.
But outside the court,
I'm a mere man.
I want to live my life
the way I want it.
Will you truly defy me
again and again
for a mere woman?
Chu Yu has risked her life
for this country.
And now, she's trying
to get back the Eldest Princess.
A woman like her
isn't the mere woman
you think she is.
How dare you!
I am just
telling the truth.
Wei Yun,
if I really
strip you of your noble title,
would you not care at all?
My...
My conscience is clear.
Wei Zhong,
how could you have
this kind of son?
(Huang's Noodle Shop)
A runaway horse!
Move. Move now.
The horse is spooked!
Run!
Mother.
- Mother!
- Runaway horse!
Mother!
Little girl,
are you alright?
Babe.
Babe, are you alright?
Face.
Your face.
Miss, your face.
It's bleeding.
Mother.
Yu, be gentle.
Are you taking revenge on me?
Right.
I'm taking revenge.
Will it leave a scar?
You're always a lover of beauty.
It is
so unlike you.
Or what should I do?
Cry my eyes out?
Yu,
a scar for a little girl.
It's worth it.
In the next few days,
Quan'er and I will live here.
Don't tell
Mother or Linyang.
Will Linyang praise me?
Of course, he will.
What about you?
What do you think of me?
Before,
I always wanted you
to be considerate
and generous.
Now, seeing this,
I know you've grown up.
You're my good sister.
Of course, I am.
Come on.
You go back and rest.
Don't get the wound wet tonight.
Tomorrow, I'll apply ointment
after breakfast.
Alright. You go back now.
Go to bed early.
Jin.
Jin, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
But I can tell
you're crying.
Jin.
Don't worry.
You won't be hurt for nothing.
One must pay a price.
I'm going right away
to find out who hurt you.
Jin.
That guy hurt my girl.
I will skin him!
I'll scratch his face now.
And I'll get him here
to apologize to you.
Wait for me, Jin.
Come back.
I know.
You aren't crying because you regret
saving that girl.
Instead,
you must be very proud
of saving her.
But you must be sad
for a scratched face.
I understand.
How about this?
Lean on my shoulder.
Cry out as loud you want.
It's no big deal.
Come on.
I've already stopped crying.
Why are you suddenly
staring at me like that?
Jin,
I like you.
It's not about your looks.
You don't need to hide anything from me.
Do you remember
when we first met
at Yun's banquet?
Back then, I saw
a flame in your eyes.
You were dazzling in the crowd.
For the first time in my life,
I got to know
what it felt like to fall in love.
Why are you saying this?
I just want you to know.
In my heart, you're indispensable.
In Qingzhou,
your slap woke me up.
After that,
you accompanied me when I rose.
It was you
who gave me a real second life.
I once said
I wanted to make you proud.
But now,
you're making me proud.
I don't care
if it leaves a scar.
However many wrinkles
you have on your face in the future,
I'll always love you.
In my heart,
you are the best
and the prettiest
in this world.
In the future,
will you not have
many wrinkles?
I will.
I will have more.
Yu.
How is your sister?
I'm afraid it'll leave a scar.
She must be very sad.
She just pretended she didn't care.
She has really been mature.
And why did you come back so late?
Did His Majesty rebuke you?
No, he didn't.
He asked me what I really thought.
I said I wanted a peaceful life
with a proper house
and regular meals.
Why does it sound
so familiar?
Are you copying off me?
That makes no difference.
What makes you so hesitant?
Yu,
even if the whole world hinders us,
I will not give in.
It's late.
Why are you here?
I want to give you a dress.
See if it fits you.
You know my size
very well.
I want you to try it on.
I have never liked red.
I don't want this gift.
It's the King's gift.
Even if you don't like it,
you have to accept it.
Zhao Yue,
you're angry about court affairs.
Punish your officials if you dare.
Don't vent your anger on me.
Are you determined
to defy me?
I'm not the only one defying you.
Alright.
Since you don't put it on,
you won't see me anymore.
Don't bring her to me
until she puts the dress on.
Before that,
she must not go out.
Yes.
(Yifen Hall)
(Changming,)
(I'm giving you this red dress)
(to let you know.)
(In my heart,)
(only you're worthy of the red color.)
(Even if I marry someone else,)
(that's just for national stability)
(and our future.)
(Can you understand?)
(Chengqing Gate)
(Different Hours)
(Early You hour)
You have been serving me for years.
You should be aware
of the difficulties I face.
Back then, we lost three cities.
Even Huajing City
almost became a border town.
If I didn't prioritize the military
and win a few important battles,
I would lose the people's support.
As long as North Qi exists,
battles are unavoidable.
I know.
Besides the war,
foreign and domestic affairs
need money as well.
But what can I do?
I gave Gu Chusheng
two consecutive promotions.
And I made Wei Yun
the God of War of Great Sui.
These...
I'm not doing
all these things
just to pave the way for Huan.
I'm also trying to build two pillars
for our country.
It's no longer about politics.
Your Majesty, I'm sorry
I can't share your burden.
Please forgive me.
Over all these years,
you have done
a lot of things for me.
So, I often
turn a blind eye
to your mistakes.
You shielded Yao Yong
and tried to exterminate the Wei family.
You even colluded with North Qi spies
and almost killed my officials.
You shouldn't have done it.
I know I was wrong.
Grand Tutor Xie
once warned me
not to be bewitched by power.
But I...
I failed to stop in time.
But Your Majesty,
I have made many mistakes.
I've also made contributions.
I won't ask for mercy.
But Your Majesty, I beg you
to spare my daughter Linlang.
I grant you permission
to return to your hometown.
This is the end of all these things.
(Zi hour and Chou hour)
(Xuanzheng Hall)
"As the emperor, I hereby confer.
Gu Chusheng, Minister of Personnel,
is intelligent enough
to have made great contributions.
I'm quite relieved.
Now, I make him the Chancellor."
(Chancellor)
Thank you, Your Majesty.
He came back from Qingzhou
and had two consecutive promotions.
Now, he's the head of all officials.
This is unfair.
Why is it unfair?
Young Marquis Wei
killed the King of North Qi.
But he was so arrogant
that he defied His Majesty in court.
So, it's natural
that His Majesty dislikes him.
Yun,
I really hate it
when he's so successful.
I will ask His Majesty
for an explanation on this.
I...
I have something to report.
The Eldest Princess is a noble princess.
But now, she's trapped in North Qi.
I suggest sending a delegation
to negotiate with its new king Zhao Yue
and bring back Her Highness.
It can break the situation
where North Qi restrains us
with Her Highness.
Meanwhile,
it'll show our strength.
Your Majesty,
Zhao Yue lurked in here for years.
Her Highness failed to detect that
and even favored him.
Zhao Yue killed
many of our loyal officials.
Her Highness kept a crocodile as a pet.
Besides, this journey will be dangerous.
Your Majesty,
I don't think
it's worth it to send a delegation
to rescue Her Highness.
Now,
North Qi and our country
both need time to recuperate.
So, peace talks are a wider trend.
But we need to seriously consider
who will be sent
and how they'll negotiate.
We'll discuss it later.
- Yes.
After you, Mr. Li.
Alright.
Wait, Your Lordship.
A new broom sweeps clean.
We haven't rested yet.
Chancellor, are you sweeping already?
You have a successful career
and keeps rising.
But if you want me
to congratulate you
on every promotion,
do you think
you get promoted for me?
You're wise, Your Lordship.
You must know
why I was promoted this time.
I even
need to thank you.
You took advantage of us.
Instead of keeping a low profile,
you're showing off.
Wenchang,
His Majesty decides
whether an official
is promoted or demoted.
Don't be unreasonable.
We'd better not get involved.
Let's go.
- Shilan.
- Come on.
Chancellor Gu,
get to the point.
You have made
unparalleled contributions.
You deserved a place in history.
But you defied His Majesty.
What if all your hard work
goes down the drain?
I don't fight battles
for noble titles
or a place in history.
Now, I only want to protect
our people,
Chu Yu,
and my family.
But one can't do whatever he wants
unless he enjoys the highest status.
A wise man foresees risks.
Your Lordship,
I believe
you're a wise man.
Chancellor Gu,
this is none of your concern.
♪If not for dreams by windswept flight♪
♪How would my hand find yours tonight?♪
♪This moonlit glow, in dusk's soft veil♪
♪Hears heartbeats tell their secret tale♪
♪Thoughts ablaze like beacon's fire♪
♪Outline your form in golden lyre♪
♪Through thorns we've trod and trials passed♪
♪Each grief and joy forever cast♪
♪Let the fierce warmth within your gaze♪
♪Melt this war-torn world's cruel maze♪
♪Still through the frost, I'll walk with you♪
♪Our mountains and our streams anew♪
♪Dawns greet the spring we longed to see♪
♪Through meadows where wild larks soar free♪
♪Let countless sails cross this worldly tide♪
♪When lonely shadows turn to two♪
♪Through countless turns and all we've borne♪
♪No regret ever could be sworn♪
♪Dawns greet the spring we longed to see♪
♪Beneath heaven's vault, in harmony♪
♪Let tears now fall for yesterday's strife♪
♪We've reached this blossom-covered hill♪
♪I'll follow you through every dream♪